<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cardiff Tour Guide App</string>

    <string name="Travel_Fragment_Title">Travel</string>
    <string name="StDavids_Fragment_Title">St Davids</string>
    <string name="Bay_Fragment_Title">Cardiff Bay</string>
    <string name="Castles_Fragment_Title">Castles</string>

    <string name="Cardiff">Cardiff Castle</string>
    <string name="Caerphilly">Caerphilly Castle</string>
    <string name="Coch">Castell Coch</string>
    <string name="Ogmore">Ogmore Castle</string>
    <string name="Ruperra">Ruperra Castle</string>
    <string name="Cardiff_Des">Cardiff Castle is one of Wales’ leading heritage attractions and a
        site of international significance. Located within beautiful parklands at the heart of the
        capital, Cardiff Castle’s walls and fairytale towers conceal 2,000 years of history.</string>
    <string name="Caerphilly_Des">This stone behemoth, surrounded by a series of moats and watery
        islands was the brainchild of Gilbert ‘the Red’ de Clare, a redheaded nobleman of Norman
        descent. He also built the original Castell Coch, ‘Red Castle’, located the other side of
        Caerphilly mountain.</string>
    <string name="Coch_Des">While resting on ancient foundations, Castell Coch (Red Castle) is
        relatively modern, the by-product of a vivid Victorian imagination, assisted by untold wealth.
        The Middle Ages fascinated the Victorians as much as the Victorians fascinate us today. High
        Gothic was the order of the day.</string>
    <string name="Ogmore_Des">Substantial remains of a Norman stone-built castle, raised by the de
        Londres family. The initial earthwork castle was established by William de Londres, soon
        after 1100.</string>
    <string name="Ruperra_Des">Built in 1626 by Sir Thomas Morgan, Steward to the Earl of Pembroke,
        it was one of the first of the \'mock\' castles to be built in Wales. King Charles I spent two
        nights at Ruperra Castle in 1645 shortly after the Battle of Naseby. Resultantly the royal
        coat of arms was added to the decoration on the South Porch, and the present public footpath
        from Rudry to the Castle is still known as "King's Drive."</string>
    <string name="Cardiff_Location"><u>CF10 3RB</u></string>
    <string name="Caerphilly_Location"><u>CF83 1JD</u></string>
    <string name="Coch_Location"><u>CF15 7JS</u></string>
    <string name="Ogmore_Location"><u>CF32 0</u></string>
    <string name="Ruperra_Location"><u>NP10 8GG</u></string>

    <string name="Cardiff_by_car_title">By Car</string>
    <string name="Cardiff_by_Air_title">By Air</string>
    <string name="Cardiff_by_train_title">By Train</string>
    <string name="Cardiff_by_car_des">Cardiff is easily accessible via the M4 motorway, which runs
        through the north of the city, making London a comfortable drive away. From the Midlands,
        the North of England and Scotland it is a straightforward drive via the M6, M5 and M50/M4.
        From the South and South West of England the approach is by M5 and M4. Access from West
        Wales is by M4.</string>
    <string name="Cardiff_by_Air_des">Cardiff Airport is 12 miles west of the city centre and 10 miles
        from Junction 33 of the M4. The airport has direct flights to over 50 destinations and
        connecting flights to over 800 destinations worldwide. Airlines operating from Cardiff
        include KLM, Aer Lingus, Flybe, Vueling and Ryanair.</string>
    <string name="Cardiff_by_train_des">Cardiff has direct rail links to many cities in the UK including
        London, Birmingham, Manchester, Nottingham, Bristol and Southampton. The journey time from
        London Paddington to Cardiff is just over 2 hours and leaves every 30 minutes.</string>
    <string name="Cardiff_by_car_location">CF10 2EN</string>
    <string name="Cardiff_by_air_location">CF62 3BD</string>
    <string name="Cardiff_by_train_location">CF10 1EP</string>


    <string name="StDavids_title">St David\'s   /   Dewi Sant</string>
    <string name="StDavids_overview_description">With over 150 shops, restaurants and cafes, it\'s a
    great place to be for shopping, dining, or seeing the latest movie releases</string>
    <string name="StDavids_overview_location">CF10 2EN</string>
    <string name="JL_title">John Lewis</string>
    <string name="JL_des">John Lewis is a premium department store stocking a range of electricals,
        home products and fashion. Never Knowingly Undersold on price, quality and service.</string>
    <string name="Hollister_title">Hollister</string>
    <string name="Hollister_des">HCo. - Hollister is the fantasy of Southern California. It is the
        feeling of chilling on the beach with your friends. Young, spirited, with a sense of humour,
        Hollister never takes itself too seriously. The laidback lifestyle and wholesome image
        combine to give Hollister an energy that’s effortlessly cool. Hollister brings Southern
        California to the world.</string>
    <string name="Accessorize_title">Accessorize</string>
    <string name="Accessorize_des">In 1984, Accessorize stylishly arrived on the British high street
        as a pioneering stand-alone accessory wonderland. From starting life in London’s Covent
        Garden Piazza as an accessory emporium, Accessorize has grown into a high street accessories
        phenomenon, boasting a massive 500 stores in over 50 countries.</string>
    <string name="AllSaints_title">AllSaints</string>
    <string name="AllSaints_des">AllSaints is a British fashion label that captures the creative
        attitude and independent spirit of East London through its menswear, womenswear and
        accessories. From the brand’s iconic biker jackets to crafted knitwear and premium leather
        pieces, AllSaints offers a consistent focus on innovation and design to create original
        and desirable collections season after season online and in-store.</string>


    <string name="Bay_title">Cardiff Bay</string>
    <string name="Bay_des">Europe\'s Largest Waterfront Development. For a great day out visit
        with Restaurants, Bars, Hotels, Attractions, Tours and much more</string>
    <string name="Bay_location">CF10 5BS</string>
    <string name="Barrage_title">Cardiff Bay Barrage</string>
    <string name="Barrage_des">The Cardiff Bay Barrage itself is 1.1km long and extends from Cardiff
        docks in the north to Penarth in the south. This major civil engineering construction project
        subsequently led to the impoundment of the bay that has over 13km of waterfront. The barrage
        includes locks and bridges, sluice gates, and a fish pass. The landscaped embankment is a
        public open space where visitors can walk and picnic with excellent views out over the sea
        and the bay.</string>
    <string name="Norwegian_Church_title">The Norwegian Church</string>
    <string name="Norwegian_Church_des">The Norwegian Church Arts Centre is one of the landmark
        buildings situated in Cardiff Bay and has panoramic views over the waterfront. Formerly a
        Church for Norwegian Sailors, the iconic building dates back to the industrial revolution,
        when Cardiff Docks was the world’s greatest exporter of coal</string>
    <string name="Doctor_Who_title">Doctor Who Experience</string>
    <string name="Doctor_Who_des">Star in your very own Doctor Who Experience adventure. Join the
        Twelfth Doctor on a spectacular, interactive adventure through space and time. Beginning at
        the Gallifrey Museum, embark on a journey to the heart of the TARDIS and help the Doctor
        grapple with a threat that could destroy the universe forever.</string>
    <string name="Techniquest_title">Techniquest</string>
    <string name="Techniquest_des">Techniquest is the UK’s longest established science centre.
        Founded in 1985, by Professor John Beetlestone and his colleagues from Cardiff University.</string>
    <string name="Millennium_Centre_title">Wales Millennium Centre</string>
    <string name="Millennium_Centre_des">Wales Millennium Centre is Wales’ national home for the
        performing arts in Cardiff Bay. One of the UK’s top cultural attractions and home to eight
        resident partners, this Welsh landmark stages musicals, opera, ballet, circus and
        contemporary dance alongside the UK’s largest programme of free performances.</string>

    <string name="postcode">Postcode:</string>

    <string name="locationDummyText">This will contain the address details which will launch a map app</string>
    <string name="descriptionDummyText">This is the description of the castle. It may contain some historical information or other relevant details.</string>
    <string name="titleDummyText">Test Castle</string>
</resources>
