<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CardiffTourGuideApp</string>
    <string name="Travel_Fragment_Title">Travel</string>
    <string name="StDavids_Fragment_Title">St Davids</string>
    <string name="Bay_Fragment_Title">Cardiff Bay</string>
    <string name="Castles_Fragment_Title">Castles</string>
    <string name="Cardiff">Cardiff Castle</string>
    <string name="Caerphilly">Caerphilly Castle</string>
    <string name="Coch">Castell Coch</string>
    <string name="Ogmore">Ogmore Castle</string>
    <string name="Ruperra">Ruperra Castle</string>
    <string name="Cardiff_Des">Cardiff Castle is one of Wales’ leading heritage attractions and a
        site of international significance. Located within beautiful parklands at the heart of the
        capital, Cardiff Castle’s walls and fairytale towers conceal 2,000 years of history.</string>
    <string name="Caerphilly_Des">This stone behemoth, surrounded by a series of moats and watery
        islands was the brainchild of Gilbert ‘the Red’ de Clare, a redheaded nobleman of Norman
        descent. He also built the original Castell Coch, ‘Red Castle’, located the other side of
        Caerphilly mountain.</string>
    <string name="Coch_Des">While resting on ancient foundations, Castell Coch (Red Castle) is
        relatively modern, the by-product of a vivid Victorian imagination, assisted by untold wealth.
        The Middle Ages fascinated the Victorians as much as the Victorians fascinate us today. High
        Gothic was the order of the day.</string>
    <string name="Ogmore_Des">Substantial remains of a Norman stone-built castle, raised by the de
        Londres family. The initial earthwork castle was established by William de Londres, soon
        after 1100.</string>
    <string name="Ruperra_Des">Built in 1626 by Sir Thomas Morgan, Steward to the Earl of Pembroke,
        it was one of the first of the \'mock\' castles to be built in Wales. King Charles I spent two
        nights at Ruperra Castle in 1645 shortly after the Battle of Naseby. Resultantly the royal
        coat of arms was added to the decoration on the South Porch, and the present public footpath
        from Rudry to the Castle is still known as "King's Drive."</string>
    <string name="Cardiff_Location">CF10 3RB</string>
    <string name="Caerphilly_Location">CF83 1JD</string>
    <string name="Coch_Location">CF15 7JS</string>
    <string name="Ogmore_Location">CF32 0</string>
    <string name="Ruperra_Location">NP10 8GG</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_Travel">Hello Travel fragment</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_StDavids">Hello St Davids fragment</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_bay">Hello Bay fragment</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_castles">Hello Castles fragment</string>
    <string name="postcode">Postcode:</string>
    <string name="locationDummyText">This will contain the address details which will launch a map app</string>
    <string name="descriptionDummyText">This is the description of the castle. It may contain some historical information or other relevant details.</string>
    <string name="titleDummyText">Test Castle</string>
</resources>
